Luciano Díaz

Full-Stack Developer

Tigre, Buenos Aires (AR) 1+54 911 5910 2957

luchodiaz1995@gmail.com ≥

linkedin.com/in/lucianonicolasdiaz/in

diazluciano.github.io/MyPage_CV/

Career Summary

I am a software developer with knowledge in Web and Desktop applications. I have more experience with .NET stack technologies, specifically with the back-end, but at the moment, I am getting involved in front-end technologies on my own because I want to improve my skills in this field.

Summary of Qualifications

Proficient in:

		IDE		Frameworks		Languages		RDBMS		Paradigms	
By Work	•	Visual Studio 2019	•	ASP .NET Framework 4.5	•	C# JavaScript HTML5 CSS SQL	•	MS SQL Server	•	POO Declarative Imperative Functional	
By Academic Studies	•	Visual Studio Code Eclipse Android Studio	•	ASP .NET Core Angular Spring Hibernate	•	Java	•	MySQL Oracle			

Career History

GLOBANT, CABA, Argentina

Ap. 2021 - Current

.NET Developer

- Daily meetings to discuss the team situation.
- Maintenance and development of a tax system.
- Development of unit tests.
- Meetings with clients from abroad.
- DevOps work methodology.

Tool/Technologies: Visual Studio 2019, Azure DevOps, C#, NUnit.

TIME SOLUTION SRL, Tigre, Argentina

Feb. 2020 - Apr. 2021

Full-Stack Developer

- Maintenance and development of a billing system.
- Desktop applications.
- Web applications.
- Project models with Web Forms and Web Api.
- Databases management with MS SQL Server.
- Database access with ADO .NET and Entity Framework.
- Version control with GitHub using Sourcetree interface.

Tool/Technologies: .Net Framework 4.5, Visual Studio 2019, Git, Sourcetree, C#, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, JQuery, MS SQL Server.

Education

National Technological University, Tigre, Argentina University Technician in Computer Systems	Mar. 2020 – Dec. 2020
National Technological University, Tigre, Argentina University Technician in Programming	Mar. 2018 – Dec. 2019
Institute Mariano Moreno, Tigre, Argentina High School Degree on Social Sciences	Mar. 2007 – Dec. 2013

Languages

• Spanish (Native)

• English (Intermediate B2)